efirstbank.com 2003-12-07

# FirstBank Privacy Policy and Disclosure

FirstBank is committed to maintaining the privacy of our customers. We have policies and procedures in place to restrict access to nonpublic personal information to employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to our customers. In addition, we maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard customers' nonpublic personal information. 

We have implemented commercially reasonable security procedures for our Internet Banking Service. More information about the security procedures for the Internet Banking Service is available [here](http://www.efirstbank.com/internetbanking/security.html). 

In regard to Internet usage, cookies are pieces of data assigned by a Web server to the browser on a specific PC. Cookies help web sites recognize return visitors, and cannot be read by a web site other than the one that set the cookie. When someone returns to a web site he or she has visited before, the person's browser gives this data back to the server. 

FirstBank uses cookies to track web site usage, such as the number of visitors to our web site and the pages visited, in order to evaluate the usefulness and effectiveness of our site. FirstBank also uses cookies to maintain the continuity of your visit to our product applications and Internet Banking Service. We do not store user id's, passwords, or any personal information in cookies.

Users have the option to set their browsers to notify them before receiving a cookie, which allows them to decide whether or not to accept it. In addition, browsers can also be set to turn off cookies entirely. 

Cookies are required to access account and loan applications as well as FirstBank's Internet Banking Service. Turning cookies off will prevent access to these areas of our web site. Cookies are not required to access other areas of FirstBank's web site.

We are not responsible for the information collection practices of third party web sites that are linked from FirstBank's web site. In addition, we cannot guarantee how these third parties use cookies or whether they place or add computer cookies that may identify visitors personally. We recommend and encourage users to review Privacy Policies carefully before providing personal information on any of these web sites.

We have implemented commercially reasonable security systems to protect personal information that we receive from any of our online applications. All information that is sent to us on these applications is encrypted using the standard security protocol Secure Socket Layer (SSL) during the transmission from an applicant's personal computer. Once an application for a loan or new account has been submitted, applicants are not able to view or update the information online, but may call FirstBank's Loans by Phone Department at 303-238-5522 or 1-800-964-3444 outside Metro Denver for information regarding applications. 

For Internet Banking enrollment, once the customer has been enrolled for Internet Banking, he or she may view and update certain user information by logging into Internet Banking and going to the Personalization section. Customers may also call an Internet Banking Representative at 303-232-5522 or 1-800-964-3444 outside Metro Denver.

While visitors can use e-mail to contact us about routine issues and inquiries, e-mail may not be a secure method of communication for time sensitive communication or communication of information that is confidential. We strongly recommend that this type of information not be communicated via e-mail. 

From our web site, we do not knowingly collect or use personal information from children under 14 years of age. We are not responsible for the data collection and use practices of nonaffiliated third parties to which our web sites may link. For more information about the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), visit the FTC web site: [www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/).

Our privacy policy is posted on our web site and is also available at any of our offices or by telephoning us. _We do not sell any information about customers to third parties for marketing or other commercial purposes._ In order to be certain that information is not provided to someone who is pretending to be you, we will establish security procedures from time to time to confirm your identity. You must take reasonable precautions to maintain the confidentiality of any passwords or personal identification numbers (PINs) that you select or receive from us. We will not be responsible for the disclosure of any nonpublic personal information or any losses or damages if your actions or inactions contribute to someone else gaining access to your password or PIN. 

In the course of providing our products and services, we collect nonpublic personal information about customers from the following sources: 

  * Information we receive from you on applications or other forms, such as your name, address, and phone number;
  * Information about your transactions with us and our affiliates, such as your account activity, payment history, and account balances; 
  * Information we receive from consumer reporting agencies, such as your credit report;
  * Information we receive from other third parties, such as your employer when verifying information provided by you on our applications.

We may disclose nonpublic personal information, as described above, about our customers and former customers to any FirstBank affiliate. We will only disclose information to nonaffiliated third parties as permitted by law. We periodically enter into agreements with third party insurance providers to provide additional financial services to our customers at group rates. In conjunction with the offering of these services, we will only share your name and address with the providers. We may also periodically contract with our card services providers to offer program benefits for our cardholders. In order to properly administer the benefits under the programs, it is necessary to share only your name, address, and card number with these providers.

As permitted by the Fair Credit Reporting Act, we may share all credit information about customers with our affiliates. This includes information obtained from you on applications, information obtained from third parties by verifying the statements that you make on your applications, and information obtained from consumer reporting agencies. Since FirstBank is a multi-bank holding company with separately chartered banks, this sharing of information helps us to better serve your banking needs and allows you to take advantage of services at all of the FirstBank locations. 

For questions or concerns regarding the FirstBank privacy policy, the Internet site, or any aspect of FirstBank, please contact us by calling 303-238-9000 or 1-800-964-3444 (outside of Metro Denver). If questions or comments don't contain time sensitive or confidential information, an e-mail can also be sent to us at [banking@efirstbank.com](mailto:banking@efirstbank.com).

Any consumer customer may use the form below to tell us not to share the above credit information with our affiliates. Your request to prevent sharing credit information will not apply to information about your transactions and experiences with us and our affiliates.

If you wish to prevent the sharing of credit information, as described above, please read and sign the form below. You must then detach the signed form and mail it to FirstBank Holding Company, Attn: Compliance Department, 12345 W. Colfax, Ave., Lakewood, CO 80215. Please keep the remaining portion of this disclosure for your records. You may exercise this right at any time. 

This policy applies to all of the FirstBank affiliate locations in [Colorado](http://www.efirstbank.com/locations/viewall.html) and [California](http://www.efirstbankca.com/locations/viewall.html).  

\--------------------------------------------------------  
(Detach Here) 

Date:____________ Account or Loan Number:______________

If you currently maintain accounts with us and have previously told us not to share this information on any of your accounts, no response is necessary, as this information is not being shared.

As allowed under the Fair Credit Reporting Act, I understand that I have the right to prevent having my credit information shared among the affiliated banks of FirstBank Holding Company. By signing and returning this form, I realize that when I request deposit account or credit services at other FirstBank locations, it will be necessary for each bank to obtain its own credit report for me and obtain a new application from me. (Please note: Each party to the account that would like to prevent having their credit information shared must sign and be identified below. However, one party may sign for another account party. )

__________________  
Signature of Customer | ___________________________  
Name of Customer (Please Print)   
---|---  
__________________  
Signature of Customer | ___________________________  
Name of Customer (Please Print)   
__________________  
Signature of Customer  | ___________________________  
Name of Customer (Please Print)
